University of Connecticut, Labor Education Center Records 1981.0005
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
- Series XII: Reports, undated, 1950-1965
  - German time-study team, 1952
  - Group Research, Inc.
  - Hamilton Standards employee information
  - Hartford Courant articles
  - "What Makes a City"
  - History of Labor in U.S.
  - "Hundred Years of Labor Legislation", 1967
  - "The Foundations of Industrial Peace", Cicero Calderon
  - Industrial Relations Research Association
  - Institute of Urban Research Economic Opportunity Act, 1964
  - Instructors guide for how the economy works
  - Instructors guide for teaching the labor union today
  - Human relations
  - Labor education center publications, (2 folders)
  - Minority employment in the construction industry in Connecticut (Box 21)
  - New Haven labor education program
  - "One Year Later: The Nation's Response to Civil Disorder"
  - Opinion Finders
  - Organizational charts of universities
  - Publications, labor
  - >Schedules and calendars of educational institutions
  - Secretary of state
  - S and H Foundation, "Automation and Society"
  - Social Security
  - Stevenson volunteer and work force, 1950
  - Summer courses—out of state
  - Summer work study program, 1965
  - Time motion study course
  - UConn summer program
  - ULEA
  - Union running
  - Union tune for grievance
  - Yale study on worker pay
- Series XIII: 2014 Addition, 1946-1991
  - Annual Reports, Correspondence, Book, Film, Video Reel, undated, 1969-1986 (Box 2014.0081_1)
    Scope and Content Note
    [subjects include: Frank Connor, oral history, labor education center, Bishop Committee, Hansen Committee, University Extension Advisory Committee, 1951 yearbook, annual report 1981-1982, 1982-1983, AFL-CIO, Labor Union Charter, American federation of teachers, local 1386, proposed constitution, Babbidge, John Driscoll, Merlin Bishop, Upton Sinclair, Walter Reuther, Paul Harbrecht, Stanley McConner, Robert B. Norris, John Glynn, David Pinsky, Alfred Horowitz, Thomas Yoczik, video of volcano erupting in hawaii, flood 1936, Spring of Cromwell, New haven, war protest of Spanish Civil War, horticulture of hawaii]